八，八，三，一。
Eight, eight, three, one.
好的。
Okay.
八，八，三，一。
Eight, eight, three, one.
来吧。八，八，三，一。
Come on. Eight, eight, three, one.
Motherfuck。好的。
Motherfuck. Okay.
消失。
Go away.
八，三，三，一。
Eight, three, three, one.
好的。
Okay.
八，三，三，一。
Eight, three, three, one.
哦，你在开玩笑吧。
Oh, you've gotta be kidding me.
哦。来吧。
Oh. Come on.
你好，我是大韦恩物业管理公司的邦妮·赞恩。
Hi, you've reached Bonnie Zane with Greater Wayne Property Management.
我现在不能接电话。
I can't come to the phone right now.
你他妈开什么玩笑。
Oh, you gotta be fucking kidding me.
请留言，我会马上给你回电话。
But please leave a message, and I'll call you right back.
你好。我是苔丝·马歇尔。
Hi. This is Tess Marshall.
我在城里。我在巴巴里的房子里。
I'm in town. I'm at the house on Barbary.
我在门廊上，下着倾盆大雨，箱子里却没有钥匙。
And I'm on the porch, and it's pouring rain, and there is no key in the lockbox.
所以拜托，你能回我这个号码吗?
So, please, could you just call me back on this number?
谢谢你！
Thank you.
该死的。
God damn it.
是吗?
Yeah?
不好意思，你是谁?
I'm sorry, who are you?
什么?你是谁?
What? Who are you?
这是巴巴里476号，对吧?
This is 476 Barbary, right?
是的,没有。是的,是的。我想是的。
Yeah, no. Yeah, yeah. I think so.
你不知道?
You don't know?
不。我不住在这里。我租了这个地方。
No. I don't live here. I'm renting this place.
现在是大半夜的。
It's the middle of the night.
我脑子里没有地址。
I don't have it in the top of my head, the address.
不，我是租的。
No, I'm renting this place.
什么?
What?
我…我租了这个地方。
I... I'm renting this place.
我…一个月前我在爱彼迎上订的。
I... I booked it on Airbnb like a month ago.
我在HomeAway订的。
I booked it on HomeAway.
你他妈的在开玩笑。
You're fucking kidding.
等待,等待。
Wait, wait.
等等，你确定没找错地方吗?
Wait, are you sure you have the right place?
是的,我……
Yeah, I...
我的邮件上写着巴巴里476号。在这里,对吗?
Yeah, my email says 476 Barbary. That's here, right?
我的密码能破译保险箱。
And my code works for the lockbox.
我应该在这里的。
I'm supposed to be in here.
你打给谁了吗?
Did you try and call someone?
是的。没有人回答。
Yeah. No one answered.
你确定你选对了日期吗?
And you're sure you have the right date?
看。
Look.
是的。我是说，它看起来是对的。
Yeah. I mean, it looks right.
他妈的。这是难以置信的。
Fuck. This is unbelievable.
我该怎么做?
What am I supposed to do?
我不知道。我不知道。
I don't know. I don't know.
你为什么不……你为什么不进来?
Why don't you... Why don't you come inside?
我们会给这些白痴打电话。
And we'll call these idiots.
你介意我…是吗?
Uh, would you mind if I... Yeah?
我要上厕所。
I need to use the bathroom.
是的,是的,是的。当然可以。
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Of course.
就在走廊尽头，左手边。
It's just down the hall, to your left.
好的。我马上回来。
Okay. I'll be right back.
你介意把你的预订确认书调出来，让我看看吗?
Would you mind pulling up your reservation confirmation, just so I can see it?
万一我是什么怪人，谁闯进来睡觉的?
In case I'm some kinda weirdo, who's broken in here to sleep?
是的,是的。不,它很好。
Yeah, yeah. No, it's fine.
让我找找我的手机。
Let me just find my phone.
这里。
Here.
耶稣。
Jesus.
我很抱歉。我不知道你回来了。
I'm sorry. I didn't know you were back.
我只是在拿手机。对不起。
I was just getting my phone. Sorry.
这里是……事情是这样的。
Here's... Here's the thing.
正确的。
Right.
是的。在我看来是对的。
Yep. That looks right to me.
太好了。
Great.
也许我在"家园之家"的电话号码和你打的不一样?
Maybe I have a different number through HomeAway than the one that you called?
这就是我得到的。
This is what I got.
303 - 5……5……303 - 509…是的,那……这是同一个。
303-5... 5... 303-509... Yeah, that... That's the same one.
是的。
Yeah.
听着，我不知道这是什么规矩。
Listen, I don't know what the protocol is for this.
我也不。
Me neither.
嗯…我想我还是找别的地方吧。
Um... I guess I'll just find somewhere else.
我的意思是……是的。
I mean... Yep.
看来我要这么做了。
Guess I'm gonna do that.
我不打扰你睡觉了。
Uh, I'll let you get back to sleep.
我感觉很糟糕。
I feel bad.
这显然不是你的错。
It's clearly not your fault.
你打算怎么办?
What are you gonna do?
开车到处转，找个酒店?
Just go drive around, looking for a hotel?
我有手机。打几个电话。
I have my phone. Make some calls.
在你的车吗?
In your car?
是啊，我觉得这不是个好主意。
Yeah, I don't think that's such a good idea.
我的意思是，我不知道你有没有看清楚这个社区，但它不是…我觉得这么晚了你不应该一个人坐在外面。
I mean, I don't know if you got a great look at this neighborhood, but it's not... I don't think you should be sitting out there by yourself this late.
我是说，我不会那么做。
I mean, I wouldn't do that.
听着，很明显，你想怎么做就怎么做，但如果你想待在这里，这里很干燥，门上有锁，我完全不介意。
Look, obviously, do whatever you want, but if you wanna hang out in here, where it's dry, and there's a lock on the door, I'm totally fine with that.
这是Wi-Fi信息…谢谢。如果你需要的话。
Uh, here's the Wi-Fi info... Thanks. If you need it.
哦，对了，我叫凯斯。
Oh, by the way, I'm Keith.
苔丝。
Tess.
苔丝。这名字真好听。
Tess. That's a pretty name.
谢谢。
Thanks.
你要什么吗?
Do you want anything?
我想厨房里有茶。
I think there's some tea in the kitchen.
嗯…想要一些茶吗?
Um... Want some tea?
我很好。谢谢你！好吧。
I'm okay. Thank you. Okay.
嗯…哦,狗屎,是的。有……有人把一瓶酒落在这里了。
Um... Oh, shit, yeah. There's... Somebody left out a bottle of wine here.
上面还有丝带，就像乔迁之喜一样。
With a ribbon on it, like a housewarming thing.
这里还有一些坚果。
And there's some nuts here, too.
我只是说。
I'm just saying.
我很好。
I'm okay.
是的。是的。好的,很酷。
Yeah. Yeah. Okay, cool.
嗯，我要喝点茶。
Um, I'm gonna have some tea.
我给你泡一杯。
I'll just make you a cup.
你好。嗨，我在想，你们还有空房吗?
Hi. Hi, I was just wondering, do you have any rooms available?
是的。今晚，没错。
Yeah. For tonight, that's right.
真的吗?
Really?
好的,谢谢。
Okay, thanks.
嗯…大便。
Uh... Shit.
你知道我刚意识到什么吗?
You know what I just realized?
顺便说一下，水正在升温。
The water is heating up, by the way.
你知道我刚意识到什么吗?
You know what I just realized?
那是什么?城里有个大会。
What's that? There's a convention in town.
什么?
What?
是啊，好像有什么重大的医疗问题。
Yeah, there's, like, some huge medical thing.
我觉得你今晚订不到房间了。
I don't think you're gonna be able to get a room tonight.
我真不敢相信。
I can't believe this.
好的。这是我的建议。
All right. Here's what I propose.
你为什么不住在这里呢?
Why don't you just crash here?
哦,不。我不…我不认为那是…不,不,不。你睡卧室，我睡外面的沙发。
Oh, no. I don't... I don't think that's... No, no, no. You take the bedroom, and I'll sleep out here on the couch.
明天，我们就给这些白痴打电话。
And then tomorrow, we'll call these idiots.
把我们的钱拿回来。我们俩都可以免费入住。
Get our money back. Free stay for both of us.
真不敢相信。
Really can't believe this.
我是说，我不知道还能做什么。
I mean, I don't know what else there is to do.
我可以睡沙发。不,不,不。
I can take the couch. No, no, no.
随便你怎么称呼我，但我不可能睡在卧室而一个年轻女士却睡在沙发上。
Call me what you want, but there's no way I'm sleeping in the bedroom while a young lady is sleeping on the couch.
都怪我的教养，但这没得商量。
Blame it on my upbringing, but it's not up for discussion.
无意冒犯，但我对干净的床单有个癖好。
Well, no offense, but I kinda have a thing about clean sheets.
你真的没必要这么做。
You really didn't have to do that.
根本没必要讨论。
Not even up for discussion.
再说了，我有雨衣，而你没有。
Besides, I have a raincoat and you don't.
不，不，我来吧。哦。不,不,不。
No, no, I got it. Oh. No, no, no.
你确定吗?你确定吗?我可以……是的。
You sure? You sure? I can... Yeah.
好吧。
Okay.
你把这个落在卧室了。
You left this in the bedroom.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
谢谢。好眼睛。
Thanks. Good eyes.
我去洗一下。
I'm gonna go wash up.
是的。把这当自己的家。
Yeah. Knock yourself out.
哦,嘿。
Uh, hey.
衣服还在洗呢。
Uh, the laundry's still in the wash.
嗯…但我想，嗯，我很清醒，所以…所以我,嗯…现在要有点了。
Um... But I thought, well, I'm wide awake, so... So I, um... It's gonna be a bit now.
我想喝点这瓶酒。
I thought I'm gonna have some of this here wine.
但我不想在你洗完澡之前打开因为我注意到你没喝茶。
But I didn't wanna open it before you got out of the shower because I noticed you didn't drink your tea.
顺便说一句，我完全理解。
And, well, I totally get that, by the way.
我是说，你不了解我，现在的情况真的很奇怪。
I mean, you don't know me, and this is a fucking really weird situation.
这是完全有道理的。
It makes total sense.
但我觉得你可能想喝点这个。
Um, but I thought that you might want some of this.
但如果我在你不在的时候打开它，那…那他妈的,我很抱歉。我漫步。
But if I opened it while you weren't here, that... that... Fuck, I'm sorry. I'm rambling.
耶稣基督。
Jesus Christ.
嗯…我以为你没看到我打开就不会想要了。
Um... I thought you wouldn't want any if you didn't see me open it.
所以,我等待着。
So, I waited.
我很好，你去吧。
I'm good, but you go ahead.
你确定吗?是的。
You sure? Yeah.
好的。嗯…
Okay. Um...
嗯,这是……要我说，在铺好被褥之前，你有一个小时的时间换衣服。
Um, it's... I'd say you have about an hour and change till the bedding's done.
你能做到吗?
You gonna make it?
我到处找干净的，但找不到。
I looked around for some clean ones, but I couldn't find any.
你要在沙发上做什么?
What are you gonna do on the couch?
哦，我会没事的。是的。我睡过更糟的。
Oh, I'll be fine. Yeah. I've slept on worse.
对于这一切我真的很抱歉。
I'm really sorry about all this.
你在开玩笑吗?
What, are you kidding?
这不是你的错。你和我一样心烦意乱。
It's not your fault. You're just as put out as me.
要我再给你沏杯茶吗?
Do you want me to make you another cup of tea?
不。
No.
这次你可以看了。
You can watch this time.
我很好。
I'm okay.
所以,嗯…
So, um...
什么风把你吹来了?
What brings you to town?
工作面试。噢,是吗?
Job interview. Oh, yeah?
是明天吗?
Is it tomorrow?
是的。
Yeah.
如果你不介意我问的话，这份工作是做什么的?
What's the job about, if you don't mind me asking?
是的。没关系。
Yeah. It's okay.
这是一个纪录片导演的研究职位。
Um, it's a research position for a documentary filmmaker.
真的吗?谁是导演?
Really? Who's the filmmaker?
她叫凯瑟琳·詹姆斯。
Her name is Catherine James.
凯瑟琳詹姆斯吗?
Catherine James?
我不认识她。
I don't know her.
她做过什么我见过的事吗?
Has she done anything I'd seen?
她去年拍了一部关于爵士乐的电影，叫《蓝色轻松》。
Uh, she made a movie about jazz last year, called Blue Easy.
哦，我看到了。
Oh, I saw that.
你看过Blue Easy吗?
You saw Blue Easy?
我觉得很棒。
I thought it was great.
你在开玩笑吧?没人看过那部电影。
Are you kidding? No one's seen that movie.
临时铜管乐队的事?
About the makeshift brass band?
还有孩子们在屋顶上，玩Coltrane的歌的那场戏?
And there's that scene with the kids on the rooftop, playing the Coltrane stuff?
是的,这很好。
Yeah, it's great.
真不敢相信你看到了。
I can't believe you saw that.
我觉得太棒了。
I thought it was awesome.
她的新电影要讲什么?
What's her new film gonna be about?
是关于这个地方的。底特律。
Oh, it's gonna be about this place. Detroit.
像底特律的音乐吗?
Like Detroit music?
哦，好吧，它将是关于过去十年来这里的艺术家们，他们在这里建立了集体和创意社区……嗯，边缘…
Oh, well, it's gonna be about the artists that have come here in the last ten years and set up collectives and creative communities on the... Well, the edge of...
那里的房子基本上是免费的。
Where the houses are basically free.
这是很酷。
That's pretty cool.
你知道该去面试谁吗?
Do you know who you should interview for that?
谁?
Who?
我。
Me.
这是为什么呢?
Why is that?
因为我是驯狮人的创始人之一。
Because I'm actually one of the founders of the Lion Tamers.
你在开玩笑吧。不。
You're kidding. No.
我是说，我不是那种人，但我是他们中的一员。
I mean, I'm not, like, the guy, but I'm one of the guys, yeah.
这是疯狂的。
That's insane.
它是疯狂的。
It is insane.
你在爱彼迎上做什么?
What are you doing in an Airbnb?
你们不是有一整条街之类的吗?
Don't you guys, like, have a whole block or something?
不,是的。不,我们做的。
No, yeah. No, we do.
但我们在找一个新的地方。
But we're looking for a new space.
我在这里待了一周，基本上就是在这一带扫荡。
So, I'm here for a week, basically just scouring this side of town.
寻找我们的下一个小窝。
Looking for our next little nest.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
这不是我以前听过的陈词滥调。
It's not a cliche I've heard before.
哦,来吧。这太老套了。
Oh, come on. It's such a cliche.
那个认为爱和控制是一回事的人。
The guy who thinks love and control are the same thing.
而那个让自己变成，我不知道，某种宠物什么的女孩呢?
And the girl who lets herself become, I don't know, some kind of pet or something?
哦,我的上帝。这太老套了，太无聊了，我不敢相信这发生在我身上。
Oh, my God. It's so cliche and it's so boring, and I can't believe it's happening to me.
现在还在发生吗?
Is it still happening?
我是说，看看你。
I mean, look at you.
你的新工作已经安排好了。
You already got your new job lined up.
嗯。工作面试。
Mmm. Job interview.
我还没有得到那份工作。我不是自由的。
I don't have the job yet. I'm not home free.
看。总有一些人会在我们身上投射某种为他们服务的动力。
Look. There's always gonna be people that project some kind of dynamic onto us that serves them.
我们要不要合作由我们自己决定。
It's up to us if we wanna play ball or not.
这是我的教训吗?
Is that my lesson?
我不知道。我不知道。
I don't know. I don't know.
我只是不能再回去了。
I just need to stop going back.
我一直往回走。
I keep going back.
也许就是这样。
Maybe that's it.
或者我的经验是，只要你允许，男人就会欺负你。
Or maybe my lesson is that guys will walk all over you as long as you let them.
是的。这是我的教训。
Yeah. That's my lesson.
我不同意那种说法。
I take issue with that statement.
哦,是的。那是因为你是男的。
Oh, yeah. That's 'cause you're a guy.
我是说，世界对你来说不一样了。
I mean, the world's different for you.
男人一生都在制造混乱。
Guys get to blast their way through life making messes.
女孩们要小心。
Girls have to be careful.
详细说明。好的。今晚。
Elaborate. Okay. Take tonight.
如果我是最先登记入住的人，而你却在深夜出现……怎么，你不让我进去吗?
If I had been the one that checked in first and you showed up late at night... What, you wouldn't have let me in?
没有地狱。我不会让你进来的。
Hell no. I wouldn't have let you in.
你觉得我疯了吗?
Do you think I'm crazy?
但如果我蠢到让你进来，你会毫不犹豫的。
But if I was dumb enough to let you in, you wouldn't even think twice.
你会大摇大摆地走进来。
You would just march on in.
嘿，你就这么大摇大摆进来了。
Hey, you just marched on in.
是的，因为我必须这么做。
Yeah, because I had to.
这很可怕。
And it was scary.
怎么，我看起来像什么怪物吗?
What, do I look like some kind of monster?
不是我的观点。
Not my point.
我明白了。我明白了。我的意思是……外面有很多坏人。这糟透了。
I get it. I get it. I mean... There's a lot of bad dudes out there. And it sucks.
听着，你是要被困在别人为你挑选的该死的有毒的生活中吗?
Look, are you gonna stay locked into some fucked-up toxic dynamic that somebody else picked for you?
还是你要继续生活?
Or are you gonna move on?
也许可以找别人。
Maybe find someone else.
即使这意味着你可能会再次被挖出你的心脏。
Even if that means that you may get your heart ripped outta your chest all over again.
嗯。为什么总是女孩们被这种事折磨得心力交瘁?
Hmm. Why is it always the girls who get their hearts ripped out in these things?
女孩可以撷取。相信我。
Girls can rip. Trust me.
好了，现在它都翻出来了…正确的。
Okay, so now that it's inside out... Right.
对吧?这是第一步。是吗?
Right? That's the first step. Yeah?
然后，现在你有点深入了。不。
Then, now you kind of go deep. No.
你潜水。
You dive in.
现在,这……相信我。这是最好的方法。
Now, this... Trust me. This is the best way to do it.
不，你在耍我。这不是你该做的。
No, you're fucking with me. This is not how you do it.
-你就该这么做。-这是最好的办法。
- This is how you do it. - This is the best way.
它从来不会结块。它变得非常光滑。
It never bunches up. It gets completely smooth.
等你躺在一张完全平整的羽绒被里，你会感谢我的。
You'll thank me later when you're lying under a perfectly even duvet, here.
所以,如果,但是……看起来很愚蠢。
So, if, but... Looks so dumb.
所以,这里……对吧?
So, here... Right?
这就是我需要你帮助的地方。
Here is where I kinda need your help a little bit.
既然你来了…哦,我的上帝。
Now that you're here... Oh, my God.
你必须做我的助理。正确的。
You have to be my assistant. Right.
如果你不介意的话，拿上羽绒被…好吧。
If you wouldn't mind, grabbing the duvet... Okay.
你给我两条边，我的边在哪里。是的,当然。
And you kinda give me the two edges where my edges are... Yeah, sure.
在两者相遇的地方。好的，谢谢。
Where the two meet. All right, thank you.
好的。你明白了吗?非常感谢。
Okay. You got it? Thank you very much.
所以，退后，因为现在它变得有点…一个小…我的上帝。
So, back up 'cause now it gets a little bit... A little... My God.
这东西有点咄咄逼人。哦,我的上帝。
A little aggressive with the thing. Oh, my God.
但这样你才能把羽绒被放进去。
But that is how you get the duvet in.
那么优雅。这就是你要做的。
So graceful. That's how you do it.
你通常都是这样上气不接下气的吗?
Are you usually this outta breath afterwards?
最后……请抓住那个边缘。嗯。
The final... Grab that edge there, please. Mmm-hmm.
好,…是的,是的。
Okay, and... Yeah, yeah.
哇。
Wow.
好的。好吧，你正式就位了。
Okay. Well, you are officially situated.
是的。我想那差不多了。
Yeah. I think that about does it.
是的。
Yeah.
好的，谢谢你今晚的款待。
Okay, thank you for tonight.
很抱歉在大喜的日子之前让你睡不着。
Sorry for keeping you up before the big day.
哦,不。它是乐趣。我…我喜欢它。
Oh, no. It was fun. I... I liked it.
是的。我也是。
Yeah. Me, too.
好吧，有个沙发需要…是的。是的。
Okay, there's a couch that needs to be... Yeah. Yeah.
在这里加档，所以…我很抱歉。
Put in gear here, so... I'm so sorry.
哦,不要。不要。
Oh, don't be. Don't be.
我什么都能睡。
I can sleep on anything.
晚安,苔丝。
Good night, Tess.
晚安,基思。
Good night, Keith.
基思?
Keith?
帮助我。
Help me.
不。不。
No. No.
基思?
Keith?
他妈的!
The fuck!
哦，我很抱歉。
Oh, I'm so sorry.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
呃,我…嗯…我的门开着。
Uh, I... Um... My door was open.
我没有打开它，我…你……我不知道你醒了没有，你一直在制造噪音，然后…我在制造噪音?
And I didn't open it, and I... You... And I didn't know if you were up, and you were, like, making noises and... I was making noise?
我很……我很抱歉。
I'm so... I'm so sorry.
我要…我不打扰你睡觉了。
I'm just gonna... I'm gonna let you go to sleep.
你吓死我了。
You scared the shit out of me.
你打开我的门了吗?
Did you open my door?
不!
No!
是的。
Yeah.
哦,上帝。
Oh, God.
大便。
Shit.
基思?
Keith?
苔丝?
Tess?
哦。
Oh.
你好,凯瑟琳!这就跟你问声好！
Hi, Catherine! Hi!
见到你真高兴!我也很高兴见到你。
So nice to meet you! Nice to meet you, too.
谢谢你大老远赶过来。
Thanks for making the trip all the way out here.
是的。
Yeah.
那你来城里的时候住哪?
So, where are you staying while you're in town?
Airbnb哦。哦,那很好。的下落吗?
Oh, an Airbnb. Oh, that's nice. Whereabouts?
在布莱特摩尔。
Uh, it's in Brightmoor.
你知道在哪里吗?
You know where that is?
什么?
What?
是的。你知道吗?
Yeah. You know it?
你在开玩笑吧?
Are you kidding?
嗯,我的意思是……看起来有点粗糙，但是…不，你不应该在那里。
Well, I mean... It seems a little rough, but... No, you shouldn't be there.
你是什么意思?这不是……在Brightmoor租Airbnb ?
What do you mean? That's not... An Airbnb in Brightmoor?
是的，我是说，就像…这是一个可爱的小房子，但是…是啊，我想这附近有点…苔丝。
Yeah, I mean, like... It's a cute little house, but... Yeah, I suppose the neighborhood is a little... Tess.
我试着找过别的地方，但城里有个大会什么的?
Well, I did try and find somewhere else, but there's, like, a convention in town or something?
我有个室友，所以…这有点复杂。
And I have a roommate, so... It's a little complicated.
我猜。
I guess.
好吧，小心点，好吗?
Okay, well, just be careful, okay?
认真对待。我会的。
Seriously. I will.
我…我是艰难的。
I'm... I'm tough.
很好。嗯…很高兴认识你。
Good. Well... It was really nice to meet you.
是啊!不,我很兴奋。
Yeah! No, I'm excited.
我明天打给你，好吗?这会很棒的。
I'm gonna call you tomorrow, okay? This is gonna be great.
嘿!
Hey!
嘿,小女孩!
Hey, little girl!
嘿!
Hey!
来这里!
Come here!
嘿,小女孩!
Hey, little girl!
从那房子里出来!
Come out that house!
走开!
Go away!
从那房子里出来!
Come out that house!
是的!
Yes!
我不知道…我不能再见他了。
I don't know what... I can't see him anymore.
他离开了吗?
He left?
我不知道!
I don't know!
你能派个人来吗?
Can you just send someone, please?
我们现在没有空房。
We don't have any available units at the moment.
什么?所以没人要来吗?太太,冷静下来。
What? So nobody's coming? Ma'am, calm down.
就像我说的，我们没有任何可用的单位…
As I said, we don't have any available units at this...
大便。
Shit.
他妈的。
Fuck.
不。
Nope.
基思!
Keith!
什么他妈的!
What the fuck!
我…我被困在这里了。
I'm... I'm stuck down here.
你有钥匙吗?
Uh, do you have the key?
就在这里，但我打不开!
It's here, but I can't open this!
好吧。
All right.
在这里。
Right here.
好吧，你拉我推。好吧。
Okay, you pull and I push. Okay.
一个,两个,三个。
One, two, three.
好吧。
Okay.
你还好吗?我们现在就得走!
Are you okay? We need to go now!
你在说什么?你为什么在地下室?
What are you talking about? Why were you in the basement?
我被锁在地下室，然后有了一个隐藏区域!
I got locked in the basement, and then there was this hidden area!
有一个房间!
There was this room!
有个密室?
There's a hidden room?
这里发生了不好的事情!
There is something bad going on here!
苔丝!苔丝!放松点!放松。
Tess! Tess! Relax! Relax.
你没事了，你很安全。
You're okay, you're safe.
你很安全，好吗?
You're safe, all right?
你是安全的。好吧。
You're safe. Okay.
我不…我不这么认为。
I don't... I don't think I am.
下面是什么?你看到了什么?好吧……我在地下室。
What's down there? What did you see? Okay... I was in the basement.
然后我发现了一条隐藏的通道。
And then I found this hidden passageway.
有个房间，就像…像一个地牢。
And there was this room, and it was like a... Like a dungeon.
像一个地牢?里面是什么?
Like a dungeon? What was in there?
有一张床……好吧。
There was a bed... Okay.
还有一个照相机和一个水桶。
And a camera, and a bucket.
好的。呃，那么，有一张床和一个…什么，一个桶和一个照相机吗?是的。
All right. Uh, so, there's a bed and a... What, a bucket and a camera? Yeah.
我去看看。不，不，不，求你不要!
I'm just gonna go look. No, no, no, please don't!
墙上好像有个手印。
There was, like, a handprint on the wall.
苔丝，冷静，冷静。
Tess, calm down, calm down.
你在说什么，好吗?
You're not making any sense, okay?
楼下有个房间，里面有床和桶吗?
So, there's a room downstairs with a bed and a bucket in it?
这是一个地下室。里面都是垃圾，好吗?
It's a basement. It's filled with junk, okay?
听起来没那么奇怪。
It doesn't sound that weird.
如果你想去看，随你便，但我要去!
If you wanna go and look, suit yourself but I'm going!
现在好些了吗?是的。
Right now? Yes.
好了，苔丝，不不不。停止,停止,停止!
All right, Tess, no, no, no. Stop, stop, stop!
只是停止,停止!
Just stop, stop!
动!就停止!
Move! Just stop!
能给我点时间吗?
Can you give me a moment, please?
能给我点时间吗?二十秒?
Can you just give me a moment? Twenty seconds?
好吧，如果我看起来不像是把你看到的事当回事，我很抱歉。
Okay, I'm sorry if I don't seem like I'm taking whatever it is that you saw seriously.
我只是…我没看到。
I just... I didn't see it.
好吧?
Okay?
我不能因为楼下有个房间有床有桶就惊慌失措地跑掉!
And I can't just be running off in a panic because there's a room downstairs with a bed and a bucket!
苔丝?不,苔丝!苔丝，等等，对不起!
Tess? No, Tess! Tess, wait, I'm sorry!
我只是…我只是想看看。
I just... I just want to see it.
如果你不想的话，你可以不跟我去。
You don't even have to come with me if you don't want to.
我不会再下去了。
I'm not going back down there.
这很好。
That's fine.
你能…你能在上面等着吗以防我也被锁在里面?
Can you just... Can you just wait up here in case I get locked inside, too?
你能吗?
Can you?
我将等待。
I'll wait.
就30秒，好吗?就在这里等。
Just 30 seconds, okay? Just wait here.
你看到了吗?
Do you see it?
是的。
Yeah.
好吧，现在上来吧。
Okay, well, come back up now.
基思?
Keith?
基思!
Keith!
基思?
Keith?
苔丝!
Tess!
基思!
Keith!
的帮助!
Help!
上来吧，基思!
Come up here, Keith!
帮帮我!
Help me!
拜托!
Please!
基思!
Keith!
嘿!
Hey!
基思!
Keith!
回答我,基思!
Answer me, Keith!
苔丝……基思!基思!基思!
Tess... Keith! Keith! Keith!
你为什么到这儿来?
Why did you come down here?
下面还有别人。不,为什么?
Someone else is down here. No, why?
你为什么到这儿来?有人……下面还有别人。
Why did you come down here? There's someone... Someone else is down here.
什么?
What?
有人咬了我。
Someone bit me.
好的。好的。我们得走了。
Okay. Okay. We need to go.
我们得离开这里!不，不要靠近那里。
We need to get out of here! No, don't go near there.
他们就在那里!不，那是出去的路!
That's where they were! No, that's the way out!
从这边回来。不，求你了，别说了!
Come back this way. No, please, stop it!
这边走!停止它!
Come this way! Stop it!
我们必须走这条路!放开我!
We have to come this way! Let go off me!
我们必须走这条路!这就是出路!
We have to come this way! That's the way out!
别人的了……请停止!
Someone's down... Please stop!
我不会回去的!我不会…
I'm not going back there! I'm not going...
♬♬♬最好进入你该进入的领域♬♬最好现在就进入请不要懈怠♬♬联合国并不是真正团结的♬♬组织也不是真正有组织的
♪♪ Better get into what you gotta get into ♪♪ Better get into it now No slacking, please ♪♪ United Nations ain't really united ♪♪ And the organizations ♪♪ Ain't really organized
♪♪瑞基-提基-塔维猫鼬走了♪♪瑞基-提基-塔维猫鼬走了♬♪每个看过《丛林故事》的人都会知道瑞基-提基-塔维是只会杀蛇的猫鼬
♪♪ Rikki-tikki-tavi mongoose is gone ♪♪ Rikki-tikki-tavi mongoose is gone ♪♪ Everybody who read The Jungle Book ♪♪ Will know that Rikki-tikki-tavi's a mongoose who kills snakes
当我还是个年轻人的时候有人让我相信有组织可以帮我杀蛇，也就是教堂，也就是政府，也就是学校
♪♪ When I was a young man ♪♪ I was led to believe there were organizations ♪♪ That would kill my snakes for me ♪♪ I.e. the church ♪♪ I.e. the government ♪♪ I.e. school
但是当我长大一点的时候我知道我必须亲手杀了他们
♪♪ But when I got a little older ♪♪ I learned I had to kill 'em myself ♪♪
Yello !
Yello!
嘿,AJ。大卫·斯特恩和梅丽莎·赫伯特找你。
Hey, AJ. I have David Stern and Melissa Herberts for you.
爱死它了。
Love it.
伙计们，你们和AJ连线。
Guys, you're on with AJ.
-哟，怎么了?——嗨,AJ。
- Yo, what's up? - Hi, AJ.
嘿,AJ。我们得谈谈刚刚发生的事。
Hey, AJ. Uh, we need to discuss something that's just come through.
酷。有什么事吗?
Cool. What's up?
这是一个有点尴尬的对话，但有一个令人不安的进展。
So this is a bit of an awkward conversation, but there's been a troubling development.
好吧,什么?
Okay, what?
显然，梅根·马多克斯通过她的律师联系了电视台她对你提出了非常严重的指控。
Apparently, Megan Maddox has contacted the network through her lawyer and she's made a very serious accusation against you.
真的吗?她怎么说的?
Really? What'd she say?
她声称在拍摄试播集时你对她进行性侵犯，如果你被牵扯进来她就不想继续下去了。
She's claimed that you were sexually aggressive during the filming of the pilot, and she no longer wants to move forward if you're involved.
她……什么?
She... What?
电视台非常重视这件事。
The network is taking this very seriously.
这是什么意思?
What does that mean?
也就是说，现在他们要开始调查了。
That means that at this time, they're gonna start an investigation.
等等,等等,等等。飞行员呢?
Wait, wait, wait. What about the pilot?
等一等。等一下。这是疯狂的。
Hold on. Wait a minute. This is crazy.
我们不接了吗?
So, are we not picked up anymore?
就像我说的，他们会进行调查，然后决定如何进行。
Well, like I said, they're going to conduct an investigation, and then decide how to proceed.
一个调查吗?
An investigation?
AJ，说实话，我认为这一切最有可能的结果是，即使这部剧继续下去……是吗?
AJ, I think, honestly, the most likely outcome of all of this is that even if the show does go forward... Yeah?
你不太可能被牵扯进来。
It's very unlikely that you will be involved.
不。
No.
我解雇了?
I'm fired?
我认为，基本上，这是最有可能的结果。
I think, essentially, that's the most likely outcome.
他妈的,婊子。
That fuckin' bitch.
哦,我的上帝。哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
等一下，伙计们。等等,等等,等等。
Wait a minute, you guys. Wait, wait, wait.
这完全是小题大做。
This is totally blown out of proportion.
好吧，我觉得有必要说一声你不太愿意谈这个电话的细节。
Okay, I think it's important to say that it's not in your best interest to go into details on this call.
你他妈什么意思，梅丽莎?
The fuck does that mean, Melissa?
好吧，AJ，我觉得你需要冷静下来，伙计。你可以放松一下。
Okay, AJ, I think you just need to calm down, honestly, buddy. You can just relax.
这不可能是真的。就这样，我出局了?
This can't be real. Just like that, I'm out?
你在开玩笑吗?
Are you fucking kidding?
我是第一个爱上它的人!
I was the first to be attached to that!
她追上了我!
She came on after me!
好吧,我……我推荐她。
Okay, I... I recommended her.
AJ，说实话，我觉得你需要冷静下来。
AJ, I think, honestly, you just need to calm down.
大卫，我觉得我们应该告诉他另一件事。
David, I think we should tell him the other thing.
不，我觉得他现在需要冷静一下……其他什么?其他什么?
No, I think right now he just needs to cool down... What other? What other?
这不重要，AJ。你只需要放松。
It's not important, AJ. You just have to relax.
不，不，不，去他妈的。其他什么?还有什么?
No, no, no, fuck that. What other? What else?
明天的《好莱坞报道》会有一篇关于这件事的报道。
There is gonna be a story tomorrow in the Hollywood Reporter about this.
关于什么?关于我的吗?
About what? About me?
你在开玩笑吧?
Are you kidding?
这些指控非常严重。
The allegations are very serious.
哟……她说我做了什么?
Yo... What's she saying I did?
她是说我强奸了她吗?
Is she saying I raped her or something?
AJ，你冷静一下，好吗?
AJ, why don't you just calm down, okay?
不。她到底在说什么?
No. What the fuck is she saying?
是的。她说你强奸了她。
Yes. She's saying that you raped her.
AJ，你在吗?
AJ, are you there?
我再打给你。
I gotta call you back.
假设这一年的收入是年底的收入。
So, let's assume that the income we have for the year is what we're gonna have at year's end.
没有新的资金流入。
No new money coming in.
我觉得这么说很安全。
I think that's pretty safe to say.
你预计你的法律费用是多少?
What do you anticipate your legal expenses to be?
我和我的律师谈过了，我们现在面对的是两个不同的案子。
So, I talked it over with my lawyer, and, um, we're looking at two separate cases here.
还有对指控的辩护，顺便说一句，这100%都不是真的。
There's the defense against the charge, which is 100% not true, by the way.
有了这个，还有诽谤罪的反诉，我百分之百会赢。
So, there's that, and then there's the countersuit for defamation, which I'm 100% gonna win.
我要毁了这婊子。
I'm gonna ruin this fuckin' bitch.
多少钱?
How much?
他们说大概每个人要七万左右。
They said it's probably gonna be, like, around 70,000 each.
所以,140000。
So, 140,000.
这对我有什么影响?
What does that do to me?
按照你现在的消费速度，你的收入将为零……三个月。
Well, with your current rate of spending, that's gonna put you at zero in... Three months.
哦,操我。
Oh, fuck me.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
你从你在密歇根的房产中获得了一些收入…但你在这里的抵押贷款要了你的命。
You've got some small income from your Michigan properties... But it's your mortgage here that's killing you.
你是说我得把房子卖了吗?
Are you saying I have to sell my house?
我是说你得做一些艰难的选择。
I'm saying you're gonna have to make some tough choices.
我可以卖掉密歇根的房产。
I could sell the Michigan properties.
有些是赚钱的，对吧?
Some of those make money, right?
是的，但有些人没有。你可以把它们卖了。
Yeah, but some don't. You could sell those.
给自己争取点时间。但不会超过几个月。
Buy yourself some time. But no more than a couple of months.
这些都不是真正的热门地产。
Those aren't exactly hot properties.
我真他妈不敢相信。
I can't fuckin' believe this.
这是坚果。
This is nuts.
听着，AJ，我得告诉你。
Listen, AJ, I gotta tell ya.
什么?
What?
这周末，我会把文件还给你。
At the end of this week, I'm gonna give you your files back.
酷。那是什么意思?
Cool. What's that mean?
我建议你选择另类财富管理。
I'm going to suggest that you find alternate wealth management.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
你也要甩了我?
You're dropping me, too?
哦,操我。
Oh, fuck me.
他妈的。
Fuck.
AJ Gilbride找Robert。
It's AJ Gilbride for Robert.
Gilbride。谢谢你！
Gilbride. Thank you.
罗伯特,你好啊。
Robert, hey.
你看到那篇文章了吗?
You see the article?
哦,是。是的,疯狂的。
Oh, it's out. Yeah, insane.
感觉我就像坐在场边，看着事情失去控制。
Feel like I'm sittin' on the sideline, just watching this thing spiral out of control.
罗伯特,坚持下去。等等,等等,等等。
Robert, hang on. Wait, wait, wait.
我把免提开了。
I'm just gonna put you on speaker.
坐进租来的车里。等一等。
Getting in a rental. Hold on.
你听到我吗?
You hear me?
我听到你。
I hear you.
我只是想说，如果我能和她谈谈，我也许能把这事扼杀在摇篮里。
Uh, I was just saying, if I could just have, like, a conversation with her, I could probably nip this whole thing in the bud.
绝对不是。
Absolutely not.
你在任何情况下都不能联系她。
Under no circumstances are you to contact her.
如果我打电话给她，说…听我的。
If I just call her and just be like... Listen to me.
在这个时候，你给她打电话除了给你带来更多麻烦外，不会有任何结果。
There's zero chance, at this point, that you calling her is gonna bring about anything but more problems for you.
你听到了吗?嗯。嗯。
Do you hear me? Mmm-hmm. Mmm-hmm.
从现在起任何沟通都要通过我们…等待,我很抱歉。
Any communication goes through us from now on... Wait, I'm sorry.
你说你要租房子是什么意思?租金多少?
What do you mean you're getting into the rental? What rental?
我在底特律。我租了一辆车。
Uh, I'm in Detroit. I rented a car.
你在密歇根州的底特律?
You're in Detroit, Michigan?
是的。什么?
Yeah. What?
AJ，你不能离开这个州。
AJ, you aren't supposed to leave the state.
为什么不呢?我没有被捕。
Why not? I'm not under arrest.
我被允许旅行。
I'm allowed to travel.
这是不可取的。
This is not advisable.
你真的需要待在这里以防事态发展。
You really need to be here in case there are developments.
“发展?”
"Developments?"
你觉得他们会逮捕我吗?
You think they're gonna arrest me?
我认为这是一个非常明显的可能性。
I think that is a very distinct possibility.
我觉得现在飞到另一个州不太好看。
I think that flying off to another state is not a good look right now.
罗伯特，我不知道该怎么说，但是，除非你打算无偿帮我，否则我得先凑点钱了。
Well, Robert, I don't know how to say this, but, um, unless you plan on taking me on pro bono, uh, I'm gonna have to scrape up some money.
你知道，我不是在潜逃。
You know, I'm not here on the lam.
我不是来度假的。
I'm not here on vacation.
我是来清算的。
I'm here to do some fucking liquidating.
我能为您效劳吗?
May I help you?
是的，我是老板。我是来取钥匙的。
Yeah, I'm an owner. I'm here to pick up a set of keys.
的名字吗?
Name?
AJ Gilbride。
AJ Gilbride.
哦,是的。邦妮说你会来的
Oh, yeah. Bonnie said you'd be coming.
嗯…
Um...
476巴巴里。
476 Barbary.
他妈的。
Fuck.
他妈的?
The fuck?
这他妈的是什么?
Fucking shit is this?
他妈的,伙计?
The fuck, dude?
喂?
Hello?
大韦恩物业管理公司。
Greater Wayne Property Management.
嘿。是的,是的。
Hey. Yeah, yeah.
邦妮,AJ。
Bonnie, it's AJ.
AJ吗?
AJ?
Gilbride从…哦,AJ。你好。正确的。嗯…现在有人住在这里吗?
Gilbride from... Oh, AJ. Hi. Right. Um... Is someone staying here at the moment?
我不这么想。
I don't think so.
哦,有人来了。
Well, someone's here.
有个手提箱，衣服，还有东西。
There's a suitcase, and clothes, and shit.
是的,没有。人们呆在这里。
Yeah, no. People are staying here.
我不…我的意思是……我们已经有几周没租出去了。
I don't... I mean... We haven't rented it out in a couple of weeks.
知道最后一批房客什么时候退房吗?
Well, do we know when the last tenants checked out?
我有擅自占用的人吗?这个…你是说自从上一批房客之后就没人来看过这里了吗?
Do I have squatters? This... I mean, are you saying that no one's come by to look at this place since the last tenants?
没有女佣之类的吗?
Like, no maid or anything?
在下一批房客到来之前，女佣们来收拾房子。
The maids come to prep the houses before the arrival of the next tenants.
没有新房客，没有佣人服务。
No new renters, no maid service.
这是坚果。如果有人把这地方搞砸了呢?
That's nuts. What if somebody trashed the place?
如何……我怎么知道?
How... How would I know?
这地方被毁了吗?
Is the place trashed?
不,邦妮。这地方没有被毁。
No, Bonnie. The place isn't trashed.
这不是重点。重点是…这是什么制度?这是他妈的白痴。
That's not the point. The point is it's... What kind of system is that? It's fucking idiotic.
我也不知道你为什么这么冷静。
I also don't know why you're so calm.
祝您有愉快的一天。
Have a nice day.
到底是谁住在我家里?
So, who the fuck is staying in my house?
喂?
Hello?
伙计。
Dude.
AJ，我听不到。
AJ, I can't hear you.
听起来就像你在赛车里。
It sounds like you're in a racecar.
我正在洗脸。
I'm washing my face.
什么?
What?
我正在洗脸。
I'm washing my face.
你能别说了吗?
Well, could you stop, please?
快乐吗?
Happy?
我当然不高兴了。
Of course I'm not happy.
我不知道该怎么跟别人说。
I don't know what to tell people.
你想让我们说什么?
What do you want us to say?
我不知道，妈妈。
I don't know, Mom.
就说她是个撒谎的婊子。
Just say she's a lying fuckin' bitch.
哦,不说话…别这么说。
Oh, don't talk... Don't talk like that.
什么?她是。
What? She is.
这不是好。
That's not nice.
“不错,”真的吗?
"Nice," really?
毁掉我的事业和声誉也不是“好事”。
Ruining my career and reputation isn't "nice," either.
我想我完全有权利叫她“婊子”。
I think I'm well within my rights to call her a "fuckin' bitch."
我知道,亲爱的。
I know, sweetie.
我知道你不会做那些事。
I know you wouldn't do those things.
你什么时候回家?
When are you coming back home?
到底特律只要四个小时的飞机。
It's only a four-hour flight to Detroit.
你父亲和我想见你。
You father and I want to see you.
真的吗?爸爸要见我?
Really? Dad wants to see me?
他这么说的吗?
Did he say that?
你知道他是什么样的人。他只是……他心烦意乱。
Oh, you know how he is. He's just... He's upset.
妈，我得走了。我接到一个重要的工作电话。
Mom, I gotta go. I'm getting an important work call.
好吧,宝贝。我爱……
Okay, baby. I love...
了什么,同性恋?
What up, faggot?
猜猜谁回来了。
Guess who's back in town.
我们能不能，好好谈谈?
Could we just, like, real-talk for a moment, though?
我们可以real-talk吗?他妈的,是的,伙计。
Could we real-talk? Fuck, yeah, dude.
好吧，你俩到底发生了什么事?
Okay, like, just, what the fuck actually did happen with you guys?
不,伙计。我是说，很明显，你是我儿子。
No, dude. I'm saying, like, you're my boy, obviously.
你说什么我都相信。
I'm gonna believe whatever you tell me.
对的,正确的。我得听你说出来。
Right, right. I gotta hear you say it.
不，我知道，我知道。我感觉你。因为我看了那个网站。
No, I know, I know. I feel you. 'Cause I read the website.
我知道网上怎么说，但是，男人对男人，真实的谈话，到底发生了什么?
I know what the fuckin' Internet says, but, like, man-to-man, real-talk, what the fuck actually happened?
哥们，我跟你说实话，好吗?
Dude, I'll be real with you, okay?
这是我唯一的要求。唷，唷，让我…这是我唯一的要求。让我跟你说实话吧。
That's all I'm asking for. Yo, yo, let me be... That's the only thing I'm asking. Let me be real with you.
我们受骗的。我们做了操。好吧?正确的。
We fucked. We did fuck. Okay? Right.
她只是被说服了，仅此而已。就是这样。
She just took some convincing, is all. That's it.
好吧，但这他妈是什么意思?
Okay, but what the fuck does that mean, though?
我是说，她是不是…她拒绝了吗?
Like, I mean, was she like... Did she say no?
她是不是说:“不，别说了?”我是说，一开始。
Was she like, "No, stop?" I mean, at first.
但是，就像，我不像…“过来,婊子。我要强奸你。”
But, like, I wasn't like... "Come here, bitch. I'm gonna rape you."
正确的。就像，一开始，她说，“不……”无论什么。
Right. It was like, in the beginning, she was like, "No..." Whatever.
但是,就像……然后我们开始更多地胡闹，然后她就消沉了。
But, like... Then we started foolin' around more, and then she was down.
像他妈的真的很沮丧。正确的。
Like fuckin' really down. Right.
我是个坚持不懈的人，对吧?
I'm a persistent dude, right?
我就像他妈的老虎之眼。
I'm like fuckin' Eye of the Tiger.
是的。正确的。你知道吗?
Yeah. Right. You know?
然后她就来了，就这样。
And she came around, and that's it.
事情就是这样，直截了当。
That's what happened, straight up.
嗨，我是梅根。请留言。
Hi, this is Megan. Please leave a message.
嗨,梅根。这是AJ。嗯…
Hi, Megan. This is AJ. Uh...
我猜你可能不想和我说话，但是我，嗯…我只想说，我真的，真的很抱歉如果我那晚做了什么，比如…冒犯了你还是……
I'm guessing you probably don't wanna talk to me but I, um... I just wanna say I'm really, really sorry if I did anything that night that might've like... Offended you or...
因为你知道，人们对同一件事会有不同的看法。
'Cause you know, people can have different versions of the same thing.
和…其实我都不生你的气。
And... I'm actually not even mad at you about it.
我希望你不要生我的气，因为我真的…
And I hope you're not mad at me, 'cause I really...
我真的很抱歉。
I really am sorry.
如果你给我回电话，我会再次向你道歉。
And if you call me back, I'll apologize to you again.
所以…请给我回电话，我再向你道歉。
So... Please call me back, and I'll apologize to you again.
好的。
Okay.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
你他妈是谁?
Who the fuck are you?
哦,是的。
Oh, yes.
好的。
Okay.
“苔丝”。
"Tess."
好吧。
All right.
他妈的。
Fuck.
喂?
Hello?
他妈的。
Fuck.
有人在这里吗?
Somebody here?
喂?
Hello?
好吧，是这样的。
Okay, here's the deal.
我有枪。
I have a gun.
我要下去，30秒后看到谁就对谁开刀。好吧?
And I'm gonna come down there and just open up on whoever I see in about 30 seconds. All right?
或者你现在就上来，我就放你走。
Or you can just come up here now, and I'll let you go.
我不是在开玩笑!那里是谁?
I'm not fuckin' around! Who's down there?
蹲在我的房子里?
Squat in my fuckin' house?
嗯?躲在我的地下室里?
Huh? Hide in my basement?
我他妈是个男人。我要揍死你。
I'm a fuckin' man. I'll fuck you up.
是的。
Yes.
最后的机会!
Last chance!
好吧,婊子。准备好被操吧。
All right, bitch. Get ready to get fucked.
他妈的什么?
What the fuck?
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
“地下房间可以被列为平方英尺吗?”
"Can underground rooms be listed as square footage"
“当卖家里?”
"when selling home?"
"至于房子里没有完工的房间" "比如地下室或阁楼" "它们不应该包含在"总面积中"他妈的。
Uh, "as for rooms in the house that aren't finished", "like basements or attics they should not be included "in the total square footage." Fuck.
“地下空间、地下室、窝点等。”
"Below-grade spaces, basements, dens, etc.,"
“通常不算数。”
"do not usually count."
好吧,“通常”。
Okay, "usually."
"即使是完工的地下室也不能计入"房屋的总居住面积，GLA， "但可以单独注明"
"Even a finished basement can't be counted "toward the home's gross living area, GLA, "but it can be noted separately"
“在该楼盘的总面积中。”
"in the listing's total area."
哦,该死,是的。
Oh, hell, yeah.
是的,婊子。
Yeah, bitch.
好的。
Okay.
好吧。
All right.
这是9乘12。
This comes in at 9 by 12.
哦,恶心。
Oh, gross.
10乘12，等于120。3乘9，那是…大便。
Ten by 12, that's 120. Three by 9, that's... Shit.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
是的。很容易。
Yeah. Nice and easy.
好的。
Okay.
哦,宝贝。
Oh, baby.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
9英尺。
Nine feet.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
耶稣。
Jesus.
哟,哟!有人在这里吗?
Yo, yo! Anyone here?
好的。
Okay.
这他妈是什么?
What the fuck is this?
好的。
Okay.
是的。
Yeah.
我们开始吧。
Here we go.
哦,男孩。
Oh, boy.
嗯…
Well...
十个10英尺。哦,我的上帝。
Ten... 10 feet. Oh, my God.
他妈的什么?
What the fuck?
嗯…喂?
Uh... Hello?
喂?
Hello?
通过寻找指标。
By looking for indicators.
我喜欢让我的宝宝决定他喜欢吃多久奶。
I like to let my baby determine how long he likes to nurse.
哦,上帝。重要的是，这个过程是放松的。
Oh, God. It's important that this process is relaxing.
不仅是为了孩子，也是为了我自己。
Not just for the baby, but for me as well.
他妈的什么?这是一个…
What the fuck? This is a...
嘿!
Hey!
狗屎!狗屎!
Shit! Shit!
那里是谁?
Who's there?
哦,狗屎!
Oh, shit!
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
好的。请。哦,请。
Okay. Please. Oh, please.
他妈的!来吧。又不是。
Fuck! Come on. Not again.
哦,狗屎!
Oh, shit!
他妈的。哦,他妈的。哦,他妈的。
Fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
嘘!嘘!
Shh! Shh!
白宫幕僚长贝克说，里根政府接手了50年来最糟糕的经济形势。
Chief of Staff James Baker says that the Reagan administration has inherited the worst economy in 50 years.
我是克雷格·托利弗，这里是NTWN新闻。
This is Craig Tolliver, NTWN News.
让你的孩子喜欢刷牙很重要，但这并不容易。
Getting your kids to love brushing their teeth is important, but it's not easy.
而且有这么多名牌可以选择。
And there's so many name brands to choose from.
但是你怎么知道哪些是没有动力的呢?
But how do you know which ones aren't motivated...
经理到收银台四处检查价格。
Manager to checkout four for price check.
你觉得一切都好吗?
You findin' everything okay?
塑料布吗?
Plastic sheets?
塑料布吗?7号楼有。
Plastic sheets? We have some on seven.
尿布和婴儿用品?
Diapers and baby stuff?
婴儿的需求是这样的。来吧，我带你去。
Infant needs are this way. Come on, I'll take you.
你的孩子多大了?
So, how old's your little one?
没有在这里。
Not here yet.
这真是个激动人心的时刻。
Oh, well, this is an exciting time.
你要带她去仁爱医院参加婚礼吗?
Gonna take her to Mercy for the big day?
在家分娩。
Home birth.
祝福你们的心。
Bless your hearts.
塑料布。
Plastic sheets.
你还需要什么?
What else do you need?
你有助产士，对吧?
You've got a midwife, right?
她应该给你一张清单。
She should've given you a list.
不，只有我。
No, it's just me.
哦,我的词。
Oh, my word.
尿布。
Diapers.
你会想要这些的。
You are gonna want these.
其他的太大了。
The other ones, too big.
你们有乳胶手套吗?
Do you have latex gloves?
是的，我想，也许吧。
Yeah, I think, maybe.
这里。
Here.
啊。
Ah.
来，拿些湿纸巾。
Now, some wet wipes.
六点九是底特律的头号摇滚目的地。
Six-point-nine is Detroit's number one rock 'n' roll destination.
为你播放当今最伟大的歌曲。
Playing you the greatest songs of today.
感受收音机的意义。
Feel what radio was meant to be.
极致的音乐体验就是现在。
The ultimate musical experience is now.
106.9，底特律的摇滚之乡。
106.9, Detroit's home of the rock.
你想买辆二手车，但信用不佳吗?
Are you in the market for a used car but don't have good credit?
底特律最大的二手车商场，马丁戴尔汽车，就在这里。
Detroit's number one used car emporium, Martindale Motors, is here for you.
不管信誉好不好，马丁戴尔汽车公司会确保你带着一套新轮胎离开我们的停车场我们不会让你屈服。
Bad credit or no credit, Martindale Motors will make sure you walk out of our lot with a new set of wheels and we won't bend you over a barrel.
马丁戴尔汽车公司是汽车城的头号二手车经销商。
Martindale Motors is the Motor City's number one used car dealership for...
劳务和退休金部,女士。很抱歉打扰。
DWP, ma'am. Sorry to bother.
没有麻烦。
No bother.
附近有些地方停电了我只是想确认一下一切正常。
We've got some outages in the neighborhood and I'm just checking to make sure everything's up to par.
谢谢你抽出时间，女士。
Thank you for your time, ma'am.
抱歉打扰了。
Sorry for the intrusion.
那么，一切都好吗?
So, everything's okay, then?
我看没问题，但如果你有什么问题，请给我们打电话。
Looks fine to me, but do give us a call if you get any issues.
当然可以。谢谢你！
Of course. Thank you.
祝你今天过得愉快。
You have a nice day now.
嗨,弗兰克。
Hey, Frank.
怎么样，伙计?
How goes it, buddy?
道格。
Doug.
听着，伙计，我…我只是想在你亲眼看到之前告诉你，明天早上我们的院子里会有一个牌子。
Listen, pal. I, uh... I just wanted to tell you before you saw it for yourself, but, uh, there's gonna be a sign in our yard tomorrow morning.
标志吗?
Sign?
一个“出售”的牌子。
A "For Sale" sign.
我们破浪,弗兰克。是的。
We're movin', Frank. Yeah.
我讨厌做这件事。你知道吗?
I hate to do it. You know?
但是他的妻子认为如果我们现在不这么做，明年这个时候我们可能就出不去了，因为，你知道，邻居们都要完蛋了，弗兰克。
But the wife thinks if we don't do it now we may not be able to get out this time next year 'cause, you know, neighborhood's goin' to hell, Frank.
你,嗯…你打算留下来吗?
You, uh... You plan on stayin'?
我哪儿也不去。
I'm not goin' anywhere.
好的。谁知道你在这里?
Okay. Who knows you're here?
我们到底在哪里?
Where the fuck are we?
有人知道你在这里吗?
Does anyone know you're here?
不,不。我们到底在哪里?
No, no. Where the fuck are we?
我不知道。我得离开这里。
I don't know. I gotta get outta here.
这是非常非常重要的。
This is very, very important.
你要保持冷静。
You need to stay calm.
你不能在她面前惊慌失措，好吗?相信我。
You cannot freak out around her, okay? Trust me.
好吧?我不想待在这里。
Okay? I don't wanna be here.
你以为我想待在这里吗?
Do you think I wanna fucking be here?
好的。
Okay.
你不能生气。
You cannot get upset.
如果你生气，她也会生气。
If you get upset, she gets upset.
“她?”谁是“她?”
"She?" Who's "she?"
这他妈是什么?
What the fuck is that?
什么?
What?
喝它。
Drink it.
就他妈喝了吧。
Just fucking drink it.
他妈的什么?
What the fuck?
这样做。
Do it.
喝它。
Drink it.
只是喝!起来!
Just drink it! Get up!
你没有看见吗?
Don't you see?
她只想让你做她的孩子。
She just wants you to be her baby.
哦,他妈的。
Oh, fuck.
婴儿。
Baby.
哦,上帝!
Oh, God!
帮帮我!拜托!
Help me! Please!
他妈的!
Fuck!
等待,等待。不。等待。
Wait, wait. No. Wait.
一个健康的婴儿一般需要…不!不。
A healthy baby will generally need to... No! No.
他妈的!不!
Fuck! No!
这是非常自然的。
This is perfectly natural.
Boop。
Boop.
好的。好的。
Okay. Okay.
哦,上帝。
Oh, God.
这很快就会成为宝宝和你的愉快体验。
It can soon become a pleasurable experience for the baby, and for you as well.
稍加练习，你就会发现…
A little practice, you'll find...
哦,去你妈的!
Oh, fuck you!
你可以预测它什么时候会饿……
You can anticipate when it may be getting hungry...
哦,上帝。他妈的!
Oh, God. Fuck!
这是我们增进感情的时刻。
This is a time for us to bond.
来分享这温柔亲密的时刻。
To share this tender, intimate moment.
你的孩子比你更清楚他们需要多少。
Your little one knows how much they need more than you do.
不要担心喂食只持续…不!
Don't worry if feeding only lasts... No!
不!不!不!
No! No! No!
哦,来吧!哦,来吧!哦,拜托!
Oh, come on! Oh, come on! Oh, please!
好吧!好吧!好吧!
Okay! Okay! Okay!
里面还有别人。你现在自由了。来吧。
There's someone else in there. You're free now. Come on.
里面还有别人。
There's someone else in there.
我知道它。我知道她在里面。
I know it. I know she's in there.
不,不,不。她还有别人在里面。我们得帮他。
No, no, no. She has someone else in there. We have to help him.
你想回去吗?帮不了他。
You wanna go back in there? Ain't no helping him.
我们不能丢下他。
We can't leave him.
你现在听我说。
You listen to me now.
你是安全的。你下了。
You're safe. You got out.
你应该觉得自己很幸运，听到了吗?
You should count yourself as lucky, you hear?
你一开始就不该进那所房子。
You shoulda never went in that house to begin with.
那是个糟糕的地方。
That's a bad place.
她甚至还不是里面最坏的东西。
And she ain't even the worst thing that's in there.
听着，你得为自己担心。
Listen, you need to worry about you.
现在，我呆在水塔旁边。
Now, I stay by the water tower.
它是安全的。来吧。
It's safe. Come on.
等等,等等,等等!不,不!
Wait, wait, wait! No, no!
我们不能丢下他。我们得报警。
We can't leave him. We have to call the police.
我没有电话。
I ain't got no phone.
她会杀了他的!我得帮他!
She will kill him! I need to help him!
你要怎么做?
And how you gonna do that?
到了晚上，她会从那里出来，她会来找你。
Come nighttime, she's gonna come outta there, and she's gonna come lookin' for you.
她晚上出来。
She comes out at night.
所以，如果你想走，那就走吧。
So, if you wanna get goin', then go.
但你不要回来。
But don't you come back.
天黑的时候你也别待在这里。
And don't you be around here when it gets dark.
他妈的!他妈的!
Fuck! Fuck!
你有电话吗?
Do you have a phone?
他妈的。
Fuck.
耶稣基督。
Jesus Christ.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
哦,他妈的。好的。好的。
Oh, fuck. Okay. Okay.
耶稣基督的人。
Jesus Christ, man.
你吓死我了。
You scared the shit outta me.
你没事吧?
You okay?
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
嘿!嘿!哦,我的上帝。
Hey! Hey! Oh, my God.
军官,感谢上帝!女士。
Officers, thank God! Ma'am.
请把你的手从门上拿开。
Take your hand off the door, please.
有一个人被关在…女士，把手从门上拿开。
There is a man that is being held in a... Ma'am, take your hand off the door.
是你给我们打电话的吗?
Are you the one that called us?
是的。我被囚禁了……我甚至不知道多久，在一所房子附近…这是72，开始。
Yeah. I have been held prisoner for... I don't even know how long, at a house near... This is 72, go.
中心委员会出了点状况。
We have a situation at the Center Board.
收到给我10。
Copy that. Give me 10.
你有身份证吗?
You have any ID?
不。
No.
你在听我说吗?
Are you listening to what I'm saying?
我被囚禁了。
I have been held prisoner.
所以，你没有身份证?
So, you don't have ID?
我什么都没有!
I don't have anything!
我不是瘾君子。我不是一个疯子。
I am not a crackhead. I am not a crazy person.
我是一个被囚禁并逃跑的女人。
I am a woman who's been held prisoner and has escaped.
我告诉你，有个人处境非常危险。
And I'm telling you that there is a man in serious danger.
你想要什么?你想要什么吗?
What do you want? You want something?
在那里。
Over there.
你想要的…好吧,好吧。好的。
You want... Okay, okay. Okay.
嗯…水吗?
Um... Water?
水。
Water.
好吧,是吗?
Okay, yeah?
好。
Good.
他妈的。
Fuck.
听着,男人。我们要……我们会离开这里的。好吗?
Listen, man. We're gonna... We're gonna get out of here. Okay?
我是说，我要走了。
I mean, I'm gonna get outta here.
我要出去，去找人帮忙。
I'm gonna get out, and I'm gonna get help.
让大家都知道这里发生了什么。
Gonna let everybody know what's goin' on down here.
那该死的东西要为它的所作所为付出代价。
That fuckin' thing is gonna pay for what it did.
别担心,好吗?
Don't worry, okay?
很快就会有他妈的警察蜂拥而至。
There are gonna be fucking cops swarmin' this place real fuckin' soon.
相信我,男人。
Trust me, man.
你想要什么?你还要点别的吗?
What do you want? You want somethin' else?
我不知道你在说什么。
I don't know what you're sayin'.
你在说什么?你想要什么?
What are you saying? What do you want?
这是垃圾。
Well, this is trash.
我不知道你想要什么
I don't know what you want.
伙计，你知道吗?
Man, you know what?
好的。这是怎么回事?
Okay. How's that?
是的。就在这里，好吗?
Yeah. This right here, okay?
我不知道你在说什么。
I don't know what you're saying.
我的手机呢?
Where's my goddamn phone?
你……你得把这个打开。
You're... You're gonna have to get this open.
女士。
Ma'am.
如果你没有钥匙，你就不能住在这里。
If you don't have keys, you don't live here.
我们不进去了。但是把它分解一下。
We're not goin' in. But just break it down.
有人被困在里面了。
There's someone trapped in there.
来吧!嘿,嘿。
Come on! Hey, hey.
你在干什么?离开那里。得到下面。
What are you doin'? Get away from there. Get down here.
你能…你能听到我在说什么吗?
Can you... Can you hear what I'm saying?
这是犯罪现场。
This is a crime scene.
她已经杀了一个人了，下面可能正在有人被谋杀。
She has killed a man already, and there could be someone down there getting murdered right now.
女士，这栋楼里没人。
Ma'am, there's no one in this building.
没人会被谋杀。
No one's being murdered.
到目前为止我看到的唯一的犯罪就是你打破了这扇窗户。
And the only crime that I've seen so far is you breaking this window.
我该说什么才能让你听我的?
What am I supposed to say to get you to listen to me?
-说真的，搞什么鬼?——嘿,马特?
- Seriously, what the fuck? - Hey, Matt?
米德兰有人开枪。
We got shots fired on Midland.
等待,等待。等待。
Wait, wait. Wait.
你们这些混蛋要走了吗?嘿!
Are you motherfuckers leaving? Hey!
我受够你了。
I've had enough of you.
你该庆幸我们没把你带到城里让你在监狱里睡一觉。
You're lucky we don't bring you downtown to sleep this off in jail.
睡了吗?
Sleep this off?
你他妈开什么玩笑?乔伊,让我们移动。
Are you fucking kidding me? Joey, let's move.
Wh……你要去哪里?
Wh... Where are you going?
在那里……你要去哪里?
Where... Where are you going?
来吧,请…求你了，求你了，别走!只是…来吧!我需要你的帮助，拜托了!
Come on, please... Please, please, don't go! Just... Come on! I need your help, please!
嘿!
Hey!
哦,他妈的。
Oh, fuck.
你怎么了?
What is wrong with you?
你他妈有毛病吗?
The fuck is wrong with you?
嘿!
Hey!
我在跟你说话呢，你个混蛋!
Hey, I'm talking to you, you fuck!
嘿。嘿，嘿，嘿，好吧。
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, okay.
不。不，不，不，等等!等等!
No. No, no, no, wait! Wait!
来吧。
Come on.
你好……
Hello...
哦,他妈的。哦,我的上帝。
Oh, fuck. Oh, my God.
哦,他妈的。我很抱歉。
Oh, fuck. I'm so sorry.
嘿。嘿,你能……好的。
Hey. Hey, can you... Okay.
好的。我很抱歉。
Okay. I'm so sorry.
来吧。我们得把你弄出去。来吧。
Come on. We gotta get you outta here. Come on.
对不起，对不起，对不起!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
好吧,来吧。
Okay, come on.
看来你的车坏了。
Looks like your car is fucked.
她不在那里。什么?
She's not there. What?
她走了!
She's gone!
她走了是什么意思?她他妈的在哪儿?
What do you mean she's gone? Where the fuck is she?
我不知道。
I don't know.
什么?我们该怎么办?
What? What are we gonna do?
你……你没有车?
Do you... You don't have a car?
是的，就在这里，但钥匙在隧道里。
Yeah, it's right here, but the keys are in the tunnel.
我才不要回到那破东西里去!
I'm not goin' back in that shit!
好的。我知道。我知道该去哪里。
Okay. I know. I know where to go.
在那里……好的。哦,他妈的。
Where... Okay. Oh, fuck.
好的。
Okay.
你还好吗?
How you holdin' up?
我很好。
I'm okay.
好的。我想我们快成功了。
Okay. I think we're almost there.
好的。
Okay.
等等，这是什么地方?
Wait, what is this place?
他一定在这附近。谁?
He's gotta be here somewhere. Who?
嘿!
Hey!
到这里来。
Come here.
来吧,男人。
Come on, man.
到这里来。好的。
Come here. Okay.
在这里。好的。
Right here. Okay.
那么，发生了什么?
So, what happened there?
你有干净的布或绷带或其他东西吗?
Do you have any clean cloth or bandages or anything?
这里可不怎么干净。
Ain't much clean in here.
真不敢相信她居然让你走到这一步。
I can't believe she let you get this far.
她是什么东西?
What the fuck is she?
她只是个住在那房子里的疯女人。
She's just a crazy lady livin' in that house.
从什么时候开始?
Since when?
她在那里住了40多年了。
She's been living there some 40 years now.
她出生在那里。
She was born there.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
那房子是我的。没有人住在那里。
I own that house. Nobody lives there.
兄弟，报纸也许是你的，但那是她爸爸的房子。
Boy, you might own that paper, but that's her daddy's house.
他从未离开过那里，她也从未离开过那里。
And he ain't never left there, and she never left there neither.
他以前常带女人去那里。
He used to bring women down there.
然后他开始和他们生孩子。
And then he started making babies with 'em.
还有带着孩子的孩子。
And babies with the babies.
你复制一个副本，复制一个副本，最后得到这样的东西。
And you make a copy of a copy of a copy, and you end up with something like that.
她狠狠揍了你一顿。
She got you real good.
我这么做。
I did that.
这是个意外。
It was an accident.
没关系。我们得找人帮你。
Doesn't matter. We gotta get you help.
怎么才能帮到她?
Which way to get her help, huh?
你们就坐在这等着。
Y'all need to just sit right here and wait.
我…我不能那么做。这是我的错。
I... I can't do that. This is my fault.
是谁的错并不重要。
It don't matter whose fault it is.
它!我伤害了别人!
It does! I hurt somebody!
这很重要。
That matters.
我不知道我是不是坏人。
I don't know if I'm a bad person.
但我可能是。
But I might be.
我可能是个坏人。
I might be a bad person.
或许我…我是个好人，只是做了件坏事。
Or maybe I'm... I'm a good person who just did a bad thing.
我不能……我无法改变我的所作所为。
I can't... I can't change what I've done.
我可以试着修好它。
I can just try and fix it.
这就是我要做的。
And that's what I'm gonna do.
我会修好它的。
I'm gonna fix it.
如果你出去把自己害死，对谁都没好处。
You ain't gonna do nobody no help if you go out there and get yourself killed.
现在，在这里，我们很安全。
Now, right here, we're safe.
她会挺过今晚的。
And she's gonna make it through the night.
到了早上，我们再考虑带她进城的事。
Come morning time, then we can worry about takin' her to town.
你怎么知道她进不来?
How do you know she can't get in here?
大便。我在这地方住了15年了，她从来没来过这个混蛋。
Shit. I've been livin' in this place more than 15 years, and she ain't never came in this motherfucker.
狗屎!哦,狗屎!
Shit! Oh, shit!
他妈的,他妈的,他妈的!
Shit, shit, shit!
过不去那该死的铁丝网。
Can't get over the fuckin' barbed wire.
等待我!他妈的来吧!
Wait for me! Fucking come on!
你的枪!
Your gun!
哦。
Oh.
他妈的!
Fuck!
没有地方可去。
There's nowhere to go.
你他妈无处可去!
There's nowhere to fucking go!
她想要我们，她会抓到我们的。
She wants us, she's gonna get us.
她不会罢休的。
She's never gonna stop.
我可以离开。
I can get away.
但你得让她慢下来。
But you're gonna have to slow her down.
嘿!不
Hey! Don't.
快来抱你的孩子!
Come get your baby!
哦,他妈的。
Oh, fuck.
哦,我的上帝。哦,我的上帝。你还好吗?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Are you okay?
我很抱歉。我别无选择，你知道吗?
I'm so sorry. I had no choice, you know?
她要杀了我们两个，然后…我没有时间思考。
She was gonna kill us both, and... I had no time to think.
我他妈的惊慌失措。
I fuckin' panicked.
我没有……我甚至都没有放手。你开始滑倒了。
I didn't... I didn't even let go. You started to slip.
我无能为力。
There was nothin' I could do.
你懂的，对吧?好的。
You get it, right? Okay.
你……你会没事的。我明白了。
You're... You're gonna be okay. I gotcha.
我拯救你。是的,你没事。
I'm saving you. Yeah, you're okay.
爸-爸。
Ba-ba.
我不能。
I can't.
我不能回去。
I can't go back.
Ba!
我不能回去。
I can't go back.
婴儿。
Baby.